去虛無的中心
I can lift this bit.
我可以把它舉這麼高!
I can.
你看我可以!
You need somebody to get the other end.
No, you don't.
不，才不需要呢
There's one tiny bit.
這裡有一根小的
Right, we need it in that pile.
對，我們需要把它放進埋裡
One more.
再多一個
Right, let me carry it.
對，讓我搬走它
Put it there.
放這裡
Put it over there.
把它放到那裡
Tiny bit more.
再多一點小點
Down there, what I left.
我有的都在這裡了
Down there it is.
就在這裡了
Right,
好
do it.
開始吧
This isn't very heavy.
這其實不是很重
I cannot lift all of those at the same time.
我不能同時間把它們都拿起來
All of those I cannot lift.
不能一次就把它們全拿起來
I'm driving the animal boat.
我要開那艘載著動物的船
I keep, I keep their food
我保存了牠們的食物
in here, in this little hole
在這裡，在這個小洞中
And I sprinkle it out all over the floors of the boat.
我會把食物灑滿在船的甲板上
The giraffes like leaves.
長頸鹿喜歡樹葉
The lions, I think the lions like
我想獅子會喜歡
The lions like
獅子會喜歡
prowling around,
周圍走動，
so I give them prowling around lessons.
所以我會給他們上周圍走動的課
What do you have to do?
你需要做什麼？
Don't!
不要！
You lifted it!
你動了它！
No, I did.
沒有，我沒有
Why?
為什麼
What do you have to do,
你要做什麼，
what are you doing?
你將會做什麼？
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
I'm making an aeroplane.
我在造一架飛機
Lunchtime?
午飯時間？
It's lunchtime!
午飯時間到了！
What is that?
這是什麼？
An aeroplane.
一架飛機
Can I go in the aeroplane?
我可以進去飛機的裡面嗎？
Yes, Can I?
可以，我可以嗎？
And we need a lift to America!
我們需要飛到美國！
America?
美國？
Ok.
可以
Can I just get a gearstick?
可以給我變速桿嗎
And I would like to be taken to Ben 10 World.
我想被帶到Ben 10的世界
My place first!
先去我的地方！
And then my place.
然後到我的地方
Then your place, then your place.
然後到你的地方，然後再到你的地方
I want to go to Fire Land.
我想到火之世界
Everybody sitting quietly?
所有人安靜坐著？
Good
好
I would like to go to Ben 10 World.
我想被帶到Ben 10的世界
There's Ben 10 World.
我們到達ben 10的世界了
At Batman World!
這裡就是蝙蝠俠的世界！
That's you at Batman World
這裡就是你的蝙蝠俠的世界了
Where do you want to go my best pal?
我最好的乘客，你又想到那兒呢
I want to go to Flyer World.
我想去火之世界
This is Fire World.
火之世界到了
Where do you want to go?
你又想去那兒呢？
Fire World?
也是火之世界嗎？
So do you, don't you?
你也是嗎？
Actually, I don't want to
其實我不想去
I want to go to Smoke Bloke Land.
我想去煙霧人世界
Girls are not allowed to go to Smoke Bloke Land.
女孩子是不允許到煙霧人世界的
cause that's too difficult for them.
因為對她們來說太難了
Can I go back?
我可以回去嗎？
I really wanted to go to America.
我真的很想去美國
America?
美國？
I do too.
我也是
Right, that's you at America!
好吧，這裡就是了，我們已到達美國！
No, we haven't even drived!
才不是！你根本沒有駕駛
Yes, we have.
我們有
No we haven't.
你沒有
Yes I have.
我們有
No we haven't.
沒有，我們沒有
That's you and you at America.
你到了，你的美國
Then to Smoke Bloke Land!
我要去煙霧人世界
That's you at Smoke Bloke Land.
你到了，你的煙霧人世界
Where do you want to go?
你想去那裡？
Fire World?
火之世界？
Where do you want to go?
你又想去那裡？
Into the middle of nowhere.
去虛無的中心
Into the middle of nowhere!
去虛無的中心！
Right, you have to get on there
好吧，你要坐上來這裡，
and you have to get on there.
而你要坐這裡
That's you at nowhere.
到你，你的虛無世界
Go get off.
你要下車了
Where do you want to go?
你想去那裡
Can I be an aeroplane?
我可以變成一架飛機嗎
This is just an aeroplane that I built
這架飛機是我造的，
and it's for me.
是屬於我的
Well, can I be a
我可以
an aeroplane that can move?
變成一架會動的飛機嗎？
This can't move.
這架不能動
If I be an aeroplane, can I move?
如果我變成一架飛機，我可以動嗎？
This is not a moving aeroplane.
這不是一架會動的飛機
I'll be a moving aeroplane.
我會變成一架會動的飛機
What?
什麼？
I move, no play aeroplane.
我是會動的飛機， 不是飛機玩具
You can pretend to have an aeroplane.
你可以假裝你擁有一架飛機
Hello Mr. Ladybird!
早安， 女飛人
A ladybird?
女飛人？
Yeah.
是的
They have poisonous wee.
他們的小便有毒
Who says that?
誰說的？
Woody and Logan.
Woody和Logan
I think,
我想...
do you think they have got poisonous poo?
你覺得他們的大便有毒嗎
No, I don't think they are telling the truth.
不會，我覺得他們沒有說真話
No, they aren't.
對，他們沒有
I'm going to tell them not to do it.
我打算告訴他們不要這樣做